## David Maldonado

301 Belcher Rd N apt. 1104•Largo, FL 33771•(727)249-3080 david.m.maldonado@gmail.com http://dave-maldonado.github.io

# **Executive Summary**

More than 10 years of customer-facing call center experience in both technical support and non-technical customer service roles. More than 10 years of personal experience troubleshooting PC issues and three years of personal experience programming.

#### Skills

•Ruby •Rails •Java •Linux •PC repair •troubleshooting

#### Education

### University of South Florida

expected class of 2016

- admitted for the Fall 2013 semester
- studying Computer Science
- regular participant of the Tampa Ruby and Codernight meetups

### Hillsborough Community College

class of 2012

- graduated with an Associate of Arts and a 3.3 GPA
- took 2 courses in Java programming and a course in PC hardware
- joined Suncoast Linux User's Group (SLUG)

#### Wesley Chapel High School

class of 2001

# Selected Work Experience

#### WMNF 88.5FM - Tampa, FL

present

• volunteer Ruby on Rails developer

#### Verifone Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2012-present

• provided technical assistance to users of stand-alone credit card terminals and point-of-sale transaction software

#### Marcone Part Supply - Tampa, FL

2010-2012

• assisted customers in obtaining the major appliance parts required to perform repairs

#### Macy's Inc. - Clearwater, FL

2007-2010

• provided technical support for the Macys.com website